Morris, James O., Office Files /4073
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Blue Collar Workers, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Women in Labor History, 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Organized Labor and the Negro, 1956-1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Cleometrics, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- American Labor and the International Labor Movement, 1956-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- American Labor and International Affairs Clippings, 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Structure and Functions, 1913-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- IUD (Industrial Union Department), 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Departments, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Democracy in Trade Unions, 1955-1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Maintenance of Discipline within Unions, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Union Finance, 1955-1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Why Workers Join Unions, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Structure and Functions the AFL-CIO Part I, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Structure and Functions of the AFL-CIO Part II - Subordinate Bodies (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Intermediate Union Bodies - Trade Departments and Multi-Union Local Councils, 1947-1956 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Structure and Functions of the Local Unions, 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- National and Industrial Unions, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Membership, 1955-1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Mergers, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Union Elections, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Labor Leaders Salaries, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Racketeering, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Racketeering continued, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- ACTU (Association of Catholic Trade Unionists), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Health, Insurance, and Pension Plans, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Labor and Politics - An Overview, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Labor's Political Record before the AFL (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Place of Politics in AFL Philosophy, 1957-1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Labor and Politics from Founding of the AFL to the Bill of Grievances, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Labor and the Republicans, 1906-1912, 1922-1972 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Labor and the Republicans, 1906-1912 continued, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- The Labor Views of Theodore Roosevelt, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Implementation of AFL's Non-Partisan Policy, 1906-1932, 1912-1914 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- AFL Proceedings, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Karson, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Excerpts from Marc Karson's American Labor Unions and Politics
- Andrew Thompson (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Adams - Age of Industrial Violence (Box 11, Folder 4)
- The 1912 Election and Wilson's New Freedom, 1912-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- IWW (Industrial Workers of the World) and Politics, 1957-1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Challenge from the Left - Politics of Socialism, Anarchism, and Communism, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Labor and Politics during the Prosperity Decade, 1920s (Lecture Outline), 1958-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Labor Politics and the New Deal, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Labor and Politics in 1930's - Samuel J. Eldersveld, 1949-1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- J. David Greenstone, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Labor Politics and the New Deal, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Labor Politics and the New Deal continued, 1945-1956 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- AFL, Proceedings, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Lewis Address, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Cementing Alliance with the Democratic Party - World War II to Merger, 1956-1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Cementing Alliance with the Democratic Party - World War II to Merger continued, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- The Influence of Party Politics on the 1955 Merger of the AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Sidney Hillman and American Labor, 1944-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Labor's League for Political Education (LLPE) (Box 11, Folder 20)
- AFL Proceedings, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Brody - Workers in Industrial America, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Committee on Political Education (COPE) - Labor and Politics Since Merger, 1965-1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Brody - Labor and Politics Since Merger, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- COPE Structure I (Box 11, Folder 25)
- COPE Structure II (Box 11, Folder 26)
- COPE Structure III (Box 11, Folder 27)
- COPE Structure IV (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Bankers' PAC, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- American Medical Political Action Committee (AMPAC), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Business-Industry Political Action Committee (BIPAC), 1956-1976 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Clippings, etc. 1956 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Clippings, etc. 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Clippings, etc. 1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  Articles from the American Federationist
- Politics Clippings 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Labor and Politics Clippings 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- 1976 Election Clippings (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Labor and Politics Clippings 1977 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Clippings 1978 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Clippings, etc. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Clippings, etc. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Clippings, etc. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Clippings, etc. 1980 Part II (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Clippings, etc. 1980 Part III (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Clippings, etc. 1980 Part IV (Box 11, Folder 45)
- AFL-CIO Platform Proposals, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- 1980 Elections - National Education Association (NEA) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  Includes a booklet of news clippings
- Clippings, NEA, etc. 1980 Part II (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Clippings, NEA, etc. 1980 Part III (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Clippings, etc. 1981 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Recent Labor Politics, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- COPE - Labor and Politics since the Merger, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- COPE's Women's Activities Department, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- 1968 Election, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- The Labor Vote and Wallace in the 1968 Presidential Election, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Wallace and the 1968 Election, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- The Supreme Court - Haynsworth and Carswell, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- The AFL-CIO and the 1972 Presidential Election, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- 1972 Election, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- George Meany and the AFL-CIO in the 1972 Election, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- ALA (Alliance for Labor Action), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Lobbying Lectures, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Lobbying - Examples of Labor Literature, 1976-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Lobbying Part I, 1963-1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Lobbying Part II, 1969-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Lobbying - Financial Disclosure - Congress, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- How Labor Lobbies - Student Papers, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Labor and the Democratic Party - Party Organization, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Labor and the Democratic Party Part I, 1956-1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Labor and the Democratic Party Part II, 1953-1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Labor and the Democratic Party Part III, 1970-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Labor and the Democratic Party Part IV (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Democratic Party in 1960s and 1970s, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Labor in Municipal Politics, 1938-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- COPE and Local Campaigns, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Labor's Electioneering in Particular Cities and Key Individual Unions, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Teamsters' DRIVE, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- United Automobile Workers (UAW) - Detroit, Michigan, 1948-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- National Maritime Union (NMU), 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Federal Government Employees and Unions, 1957-1973 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Transport Workers Union (TWU), 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (ORC and B), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- New York State COPE, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- United Transportation Union, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Labor's Electioneering in Particular Cities, 1969-1980 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Labor and Politics on State Level, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- The Politics of Assessment and Endorsement, 1969-1984 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Registration and Get-out-the-Vote Drives, 1956-1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Effectiveness Lectures, 1969-1982 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Effectiveness, 1969-1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Effectiveness continued, 1959-1976 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Major Parties in American History, 1962-1971 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Political Spending Lectures, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Articles on Money in Politics, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Political Spending Articles Part II, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Articles on Spending Not Looked at 1983, 1974-1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Finances, 1956-1977 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Labor Politics and the Law, 1939-1971 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Malbin on Labor and Business and Campaign Finance 1970s Part I, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Campaign Spending - Malbin, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Dues Opt-Out, 1968-1976 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Labor Politics and the Law, 1943-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 1976 Hatch Act Reform Veto, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Labor Political Spending and the Law, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Labor Political Spending and the Hatch Act, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Summary of Labor and Politics, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Childs - Labor and Capital, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Excerpts from Harwood Childs's Labor and Capital in National Politics
- Carroll - Labor and Politics, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Excerpts from Mollie Carroll's Labor and Politics: The Attitude of the American Federation of Labor
- Witte - Injunctions and the Courts, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Hurwitz - Theodore Roosevelt and Labor in New York State, 1880-1900 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Rehmus and McLaughlin, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Union File Inventory (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Administration of Labor Law, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO COPE Legislative Program 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Fowler Conference, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Labor and the Community (Box 13, Folder 15)
- NLRB - Politics (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Labor and 1969 Mayoralty Campaign in New York (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Labor and Tariffs, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Job Safety Bill, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Rubber Workers, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Labor and Federal Appointments, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- States in General, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Jane Addams, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Altgeld (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Harry Bridges, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Brophy (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Carnegie (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Cesar Chavez, 1971-1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- John R. Commons - Myself, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Clarence Darrow, 1953-1985 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Eugene V. Debs, 1948-1983 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Len de Caux, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- The Disinherited (Box 13, Folder 33)
- In Dubious Battle (Box 13, Folder 34)
- E.G. Flynn, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Henry Ford, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- John Kenneth Galbraith - New Industrial State (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Emma Goldman, 1955-1983 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Gompers' Autobiography (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Haywood, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Conlin - Big Bill Haywood (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Thomas Jefferson, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Jensen, Heritage of Conflict (Box 13, Folder 43)
- John L. Lewis, 1961-1985 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Jack London - The Iron Heel (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Marx, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- David McDonald, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Meany, 1971-1985 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Madame Frances Perkins, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Perlman (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Powderly (Box 13, Folder 51)
- A. Philip Randolph, 1973-1983 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- John Reed and Upton Sinclair, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Walter Reuther, 1969-1983 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Lincoln Steffens, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Senator Robert A. Taft, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Senator Wagner (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Collective Bargaining, 1956-1980 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Dispute Settlement, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Labor Force, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Job Evaluation, 1953-1974 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Wage Theory, 1955-1974 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Unions and Inflation, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Unemployment (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Famous Trials Background, 1972-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Famous Trials, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Plea Bargaining, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- XYY Chromosome Defense, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Free Press/Fair Trial, 1967-1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Miranda v. Arizona, 1966-1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Ford and Suhr, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Haywood, 1957-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Haywood - Howard Friedman's Term Paper, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- The Trial of Big Bill Haywood, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Borah and Haywood Trial (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Joe Hill Case, 1967-1981 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Molly Maguires, 1973-1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Molly Maguires continued, 1964-1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- McNamara Case, 1955-1981 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- McNamara Case continued, 1912-1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- McNamara Duplicate, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Duplicate of part of the material in folder 16
- Mooney, 1973-1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- World War I - IWW Trials, 1963-1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Centralia Case, 1921-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Sacco-Vanzetti Part I, 1963-1985 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Sacco-Vanzetti Part II, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Sacco-Vanzetti Part III, 1965-1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Scottsboro Case, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Scottsboro Boys, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Scottsboro Boys continued, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Boyle, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Hoffa, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Labor Movement - Brazil, 1951-1962 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Labor Movement in Latin America and South America Part I, 1960-1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Labor Movement in Latin America and South America Part II, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Labor Movement in Latin America and South America Part III (Box 14, Folder 32)
- ILR 405 - New Films, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ILR 405 - All Data for Films Used Part I, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- ILR 405 - All Data for Films Used Part II, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ILR 405 - All Data for Films Used Part III, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Film Sources - James O. Morris, 1970-1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Film Sources, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Songs, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Radio Tapes, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- ILR 405 - Films Part I - Violence, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- ILR 405 - Films Part II - Work, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- ILR 405 - Films Part III - Ideology, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- ILR 405 - Films Part IV - Women, Blacks, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- ILR 405 - Films V - Personalities, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- A - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Includes some Spanish language material
- Advisees, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Advisees, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Advisees, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Annual Report, 1964-1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- B - Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- C - Correspondence, 1970-1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- George Calvert - Fiscal Officer, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Efren Cordova, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Academic Standards Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Curriculum Committee - ILR Undergraduate, 1959-1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Committee on Extension, 1961-1966 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Graduate Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Nominations and Elections Committee, 1972-1983 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Committee on Planning and Personnel Policies, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Research and Publications Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations - Undergraduate Program Committee, 1964-1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- D - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Collective Bargaining Department, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- CB, LL, LH, Department Labor Law Candidates, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- ILR - Division of Publications, 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- E - Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- F - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Faculty Legislation, 1977-1983 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- ILR - Minutes of Faculty Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- ILR - Forum, 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- G - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Graduate Advisees, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- H - Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- I - Correspondence, 1971-1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Department of International and Comparative Labor Relations, 1962-1970 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Irving M. Ives - Commissioning of Biography, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- J - Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- K - Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- L - Correspondence, 1971-1982 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part I, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part II, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part III, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part IV, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part V, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part VI, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part VII, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part VIII, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Labor History - Manuscripts Part IX, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Leab, Daniel, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Leab, Daniel Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Leab, Daniel Correspondence Par II, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Leab, Daniel Correspondence Part III, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Leab, Daniel Correspondence Part IV, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Labor Historians, 1975-1982 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Labor Management Documentation Center, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- LIR - Library General Correspondence, 1964-1978 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- McKersie, Dean R. B., 1974-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- M - Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Efren Cordova - Manuscript, 1965-1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Alberto Armstrong - Manuscript, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Wilfred Haricharan - Manuscript, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Carlos Planck - Manuscript, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Shafeek Sultan-Khan - Manuscript, 1966-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Various Candidates - Masters Exam, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- N - Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- O - Correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Office of Residence Instruction (ORI) Director, 1964-1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- P - Correspondence, 1971-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- PhDs, MSs and MILR Checklists and Memos, 1964-1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- PhD - Efren Cordova, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- PhD - Joanne V. Florine, 1974-1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- PhD - Carmelo Mesa-Lago, 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- PhD - Richard Miller, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- PhD - Herb Oestreich, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- PhD - Mark Thompson, 1964-1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- PhD - George Westacott, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- R- Correspondence, 1969-1984 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Recommendations (1984-1985) (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Recommendations (1982-1983) (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Recommendations (1981-1982) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  Includes Social Security Numbers
- Recommendations (1980-1981) (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Recommendations (1979-1980) (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Recommendations (1978-1979) (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Research Correspondence - Fall 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- ILR Review - Associate Editorship and General, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- ILR Review - Manuscripts reviewed by James O. Morris, 1956-1983 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- ILR Review - Book Review Correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- ILR Review Editorial Board, 1964-1970 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- ILR Review - Professor Ferguson, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- ILR Review - Book Reviews by James O. Morris, 1955-1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- S - Correspondence, 1971-1985 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Summer Research and Payroll, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- James O. Morris - Summer Teaching, 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- T - Correspondence, 1972-1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Traffic Bureau Memos, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Travel - James O. Morris Personal Research, 1975-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Research Project Budgets, 1956-1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- V - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Visitors including Foreign, 1971-1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Vita, 1961-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- W - Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- J. Wilson, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Y - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- ILR 100 - Exams 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1967 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1967 Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 3)
- ILR 100 - Mid-Term exam and make-up exam 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1968 - Grades (Box 19, Folder 5)
- ILR 100 - Requests duplicating material for handouts, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- ILR 100 - Final Exam, Spring 1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1968 Course Materials, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- ILR 100 -Course Outline, Spring 1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- ILR 100B - Spring 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- ILR 100 - Outline Spring 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- ILR 100B - Reserve List - Spring 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- ILR 100B - Spring 1970 - Final Exam (Box 19, Folder 13)
- ILR 100B - Spring 1970 - Mid-term (Box 19, Folder 14)
- ILR 100C - Spring 1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1971 - Course Evaluation (Box 19, Folder 16)
- ILR 100D - Spring 1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- ILR 100 - Course Description, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- ILR 100E - Spring 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- ILR 100 - Summer 1975 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1977 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1978 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1979, 1967-1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1980 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1982 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- ILR 100 - Section 3 - Fall 1983 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- ILR 100 - Section 4 - Fall 1983 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- ILR 100 - Fall 1984, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- ILR 100D - Mid-term and Final Examinations, 1970-1984 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- ILR 101 - Exam File, 1971-1985 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- ILR 101 - Films on Politics, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- ILR 101 - Labor and Politics - Spring 1979, 1971-1979 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- ILR 101 - Spring 1981 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- ILR 101 - Spring 1983 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- ILR 101 - Spring 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- ILR 150 Exams, 1975-1978 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- ILR 150 - Summer 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- ILR 150 - Summer 1976, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- ILR 150 - Summer 1977 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- ILR 200 - Bibliography, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1967 - Evaluation (Box 19, Folder 45)
- ILR 200, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1967 (Box 19, Folder 47)
- ILR 200 - Course Outline, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 48)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1967 - Mid-term Exam, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 49)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1967 - Grades, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- ILR 200 - Mid-term Exam - Fall 1968 (Box 19, Folder 51)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1968 - Outline (Box 19, Folder 52)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1968 - Final Exam (Box 19, Folder 53)
- ILR 200 - Fall 1968 - Make-up Final Exam (Box 19, Folder 54)
- ILR 200B - Reserve List - Fall 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 55)